infosniper.net 2019-10-27

# Location based service - Regional Targeting Offers

Last updated: 5/24/2018

Connectica LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://www.infosniper.net/ (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

Please read through our policies with regard to your personal information. Changes may be made to these policies or our site without notice so visit this page regularly to stay updated. By continuing to use our site, you agree to this policy.

**Information Collection And Use  
**While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data  
**Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**Information Collected by Google**  
Visitor activity is tracked using Google Analytics. Google Analytics is subject to the privacy policy of Google, Inc., which you can find on [Google’s website](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Information collected and processed by Google Analytics includes a portion of the user’s IP address and an approximate network and geographic location. Google Analytics acquires all its information directly from the user, by installing a “cookie” on the user’s computer. We do not share any information we collect with Google, and Google Analytics does not collect any personal identifying information.

In addition, our site may use Google AdSense to display advertisements on some pages. Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s visits to our site. Google may also use the DoubleClick DART cookie to enable it and its partners to serve ads based on a user’s visits to other sites on the Internet. Users can choose to disable the DoubleClick Cookie at any time. For more information about Google’s Advertising Policy, please visit [Google’s Privacy Page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites).

**Third Parties**  
User information stored on this website will never be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any third parties, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

**Use of Cookies**  
Our site may use cookies to store login and session information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device. While cookies can be disabled or blocked in your browser settings, doing so will adversely affect the functionality of This Site.

**External Links**  
This Site may contain links to other websites which are hosted by and maintained by third parties. Proceeding to such websites is at your own risk and we make no representations regarding the content of any such website. We cannot be liable for any loss or damage which may arise from the use of third party websites.

**Security  
**The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy  
**This Privacy Policy is effective as of 5/24/2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us  
**If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
